Over there!
She's up ahead!
We must catch her!
I'm willing to go with you.
She must have accomplices.
Step up security.
Step right up, take a look!
How's business been lately?
In this freezing cold,
barely scraping by.
Sir.
I finally found you.
Here's the intelligence you asked for.
Please, you must save Rongcheng.
Suspicious person over there! Go search!
Sir, get out of here!
I'll take care of them!
Hurry!
Go! Get out of here!
Run!
Hurry up!
Search!
Yes, sir!
Over here.
Come on.
Word came from our informant.
Dali didn't make it.
Chen Min...
was captured by the Japanese, too.
Get out of my way!
Calm down!
Going there now is suicide!
Don't be reckless.
Here's what we do.
Baozhu and I will take the guerrillas
and attack the Japanese supply depot
to draw their fire.
You and Mingyuan take our men
to raid the Japanese POW camp,
rescue Chen Min,
and free all the POWs being held there.
All right.
Where is the guerrillas' hideout?
Talk! Where is it?
I don't know!
Are you going to talk?
Talk!
Hasn't she talked yet?
Major General, not yet.
Her willpower is too strong.
Sister Minmin! Sister Minmin!
Xiaoyu!
Look at the yummy treats I brought you!
Let's go.
Look, she's here.
Minmin's here.
Uncle, Auntie.
Minmin, you're here!
I brought you some freshly made
Meiqieyou thousand-layer cake.
I want some! I want some!
Xiaoyu, here you go.
Oh, Minmin.
As for me,
I got each of you a jade peace amulet.
Come here and try it on.
Does it look nice?
Here.
Stay safe and sound.
Thank you, Auntie.
Safe and sound.
Get the hell out, you Japanese! Scram!
All of you, get the hell away!
Telling us to scram?
Have a taste of the chili water!
It hurts! It hurts!
Tell me.
Those elusive Chinese soldiers...
where are they?
I don't understand what you're asking.
Major General, bad news!
A group of Chinese soldiers attacked the supply depot!
Yuna...
What should we do with her?
Kill me! Kill me if you have the guts!
Kill her.
Minmin.
It's me, Lian Ye.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Come on, I'm taking you to the hospital.
Brother Lian, hurry!
Patrols are heading this way!
It's too late.
How could this happen?
How did this happen?
Xiaoyu...
Xiaoyu is in Inukai Kai's hands.
Promise me.
Bring him back.
I can't stay with you till the end.
Actually, that night you came to see me,
I lied.
When I said I didn't want to be with you
because
I didn't love you.
I know.
I... I know.
Minmin, I... I beg you.
I'm begging you,
don't leave me.
Please... I'm begging you.
Getting to see you one last time...
makes me so happy.
Promise me...
you'll live on.
I'm taking you back.